Go ahead, Mike.
>> Well, welcome. Uh, certainly an exciting
day here. Um, you know, what's better
than having uh one first round pick than
than having two. Um, so, you know, we
couldn't be more excited to uh to to
welcome Carnell Tate and Kendrick Faulk
to to the Titans organization. Um, you
know, just two obviously outstanding
football players. They're even better
human beings. Um they embody everything
that we want uh in this organization. Uh
their work ethic, resiliency,
uh toughness, intelligence. Um
they have it all and that's why they're
sitting up here today. So uh without
further ado, uh we'll open it up to
questions here.
>> Right.
>> Go ahead, guys.
>> Go ahead, TD.
Uh going to start with Carnell. Uh since
getting drafted, obviously it's been a
busy whirlwind, but have you had a
chance to do a little bit more homework
to to learn about the team that you're
joining and particularly the offense and
the quarterback?
>> Um yes, since being drafted, that's all
I've been doing was just watching
videos, all the guys here. Bunch of
great group of guys that's here, great
coaches, great uh players. So yeah, all
I've been doing was just getting
familiar with the players and the
coaches.
Terron Davenport, ESPN for you, Coach
Salah. Obviously, the measurables are
all there with with Kellrick and and
what he brings to the table. How much
are you banking on you and your coaching
staff to be able to maximize the most
out of him? Um,
>> well, it's gonna be hard. Look at him.
>> But, uh, no, we we, you know, knock on
wood, we've we've had a lot of history
with uh uh um guys with his skill set
from Eric Armstead, guy, a gentleman
who's here uh with us now with John
Franklin Myers. Uh we drafted Mike
Williams a year ago. Um we know exactly
uh what to uh what's going to be great
with him with his uh how to utilize his
strengths, if you will. But uh sky's is
the limit for this young man. He's
young. Um there's a lot of football that
he's got to learn, but we're excited to
have him.
>> Terry McCormack, main street media
coach. This is also for you. Where do
you see Kelch fitting in that front
seven? What kind of how many different
ways do you feel like you can use him?
>> Yeah, we're we're um uh we're going to
roll eight or nine on game day and uh we
roll them pretty good. Um we try to keep
our guys around 60% play time at max. Uh
keep them fresh, keep them rolling. Um,
we see him outside on early downs and
pop him uh kick him inside on uh on pass
downs and that's uh uh we think he's got
an elite trait to rush a passer on the
inside and uh combination between him,
Jeffrey, u John Franklin Myers, I mean
it's that it's a pretty lethal
combination between the three of them
and um we'll find different ways to get
them all on the field.
>> Robert Paul KuharskiPk.com
um you guys have obviously brought in a
lot of defensive talent now. now more on
the line and you've talked about guys
that could start outside and go inside
and the 60% and all that. Could you talk
in more detail? I mean, you've got a lot
of guys that could start on the outside
and pop inside, but only so many third
downs to to to to do that on. How do you
sort out the wide nine in particular?
Who who's there right now in your head?
And and
even in that 60%, how do you sort out
outside to inside when you have so many
guys that fit that bill?
>> No, for sure. That's one that's why
Aaron Whitecon gets paid so much money.
Um but um but no, in all seriousness,
you know, you I I know the two obvious
ones are Jacob Martin and uh uh
Germaine, but I I think a lot of people
are forgetting about Fei. Uh I think he
you know, he was drafted last year. He's
a talented young man. Um, you know,
we're going to do our best to try to uh
to give him every opportunity to be
successful as a as a wide nine edge
rusher on third down. And, uh, we feel
really good about the rotation that's
being built here. I think Borggo's done
a great job collecting a group of men
that have different skill sets and have
versatility to them. And um look, when
when you guys start watching us and uh
you'll start seeing what we do third
downwise with regards to our alignments
and all the different fronts that we'll
create to try to create one-on- ones and
mismatches and um you know, so with
regards to the complexity of it, it it
is complex uh trying to get all these
guys on the field, but uh it's something
that we're very comfortable with,
something that we've done in our past
and something we'll continue to do.
>> Jim Wyatt from Tennessee.com. I guess
this is both for Carnell and
Kellendrick. What have the last 24 hours
been like for both of you guys and
what's it been like kind of going
through this process together?
>> Uh the last 24 hours uh they kind they
kind of been a little hectic. Uh mostly
exciting though just because uh I get to
start a new part of my journey. So um
yeah it just really been exciting. uh
came in the building today to get to
know uh some of the great people in this
building and um you know I brought my
family down here so uh they get to
witness it as well. So it's been great.
Yeah.
>> Yeah. Like like Kendrick said it's been
hectic uh the past 24 hours. I mean this
is all we ever worked for. Uh we're very
appreciative of the Tit Titans
organization for believing in us and
then they also wouldn't be for without
our parents and our family that got us
this far. So, we appreciate them all and
we appreciate the Titans organization
for bringing us in.
>> Uh, this question is for Carnell. Uh,
it's Courtland Griffin three-point
conversion. Uh, Carell, your time at
Ohio State, you played a myriad of
roles. You played outside, inside, XZ
slot. How do you feel like that's
prepared you for your role here in
Nashville? Uh, and then how fun is it
going to be for you to learn from a guy
like Greg Lewis who will be your wide
receivers's coach, and then Calvin
Ridley, who will be your WY veteran? um
playing different roles on the offense
has just allowed me to thrive and also
just allow me to understand the concepts
that way if any guy goes down I can I
can move and go to different positions.
So that just shows how versatile you I
am. And then also like with these guys
up here if they put me in a position to
go in the slot I'm ready for it. I've
seen that look.
>> Uh Junior Cooper WSMV4 this is for
Carnell. You got to meet Cam today in
person. I mean what was that interaction
like and what stood out the most about
him? Uh it was a fun interaction. Uh
Cam's a great guy, elite talent, elite
quarterback. Um great guy. Um I I grew
up watching him. I watched him at
Washington State. U so you just we can't
get out wait to get out there and light
it up together.
>> Mike Paddton uh with uh touring the AFC
South. I want to ask both of you, have
you had a chance to check out just the
offenses that offense and defense that
you're both joining? And what's the
immediate things that stood out to you
as to where you would fit in and what
you can be able to contribute?
>> Um, yeah. So, I actually got I just got
done watching a few plays uh today. Um,
whatever the coaches need me to uh go
out there and play, that's why I think I
fit in. Whatever they ask for me, I give
it my all and go out there and do it.
>> Uh, the first thing that popped out to
me was uh that everybody play fast and
violent. told um you know we said we
said edge is hard and uh we play fast
and we play violent. That's the thing
that popped out to me the most. Um I
feel like I could play a lot of the
positions across the D line uh like
coach said on on on early downs like
first and second on the edge and uh
having that ability to go inside on
third downs uh is is where I see myself
for sure.
Carell, Paul Kohhurski, you you spoke
yesterday briefly about Brian Hartline.
Could could you give us some more detail
and depth about his impact on you, kind
of the the the nitty-gritty about how he
affects Ohio affected Ohio State
receivers and you in particular?
>> Uh, Coach Arlline has done a great job
with us, a phenomenal job with all the
receivers that came out of Ohio State.
Obviously, he uh Ohio from Ohio, grew up
Ohio State fan, played Ohio State fan,
also played at the highest level. So,
all he did was pour his experience into
us and then allowed us to thrive and
translate to the next level. And he also
harp harped on details. It's like little
things with coach Hardline that get you
at the next level. So, he's always big
on that and always big on getting
better.
>> Hey, Carl. Nick Sus with the Tennessee
over here. Um the jump you took from
that sophomore year to the junior year
to kind of emerge as a first round
talent. What what were the things you
were emphasizing to take that leap and
how were you able to make that leap over
that time?
>> Uh it was just ultimately a mindset
change to go out there uh this is the
year uh this is the year I had set for
myself to go out there and ultimately
declare for the drive. So just go go out
there and show everybody who I think I
am
>> Kendrick. This one's for you.
>> Yeah. I wanted to ask you in watching a
lot of your damage it came from five
tech but you could play up and down the
line of scrimmage at at your height 66
like what is it that allows you to be
able to excel on the outside as well as
on the inside and coal what are your
thoughts on his versatility and how
you'll be able to deploy him? Uh really
just my length. My lymph is uh giving me
the giving me the ability to just go
down there and u hold my own in the
inside. Uh set edges when I'm on the
edge. Uh and then it just the power that
I bring behind it. So uh my length and
power just help me help me do both of
them really well.
>> Yeah. the the other part to it and he
didn't mention is his his his short air
quickness and his foot speed is really
really good for a man his size. Um which
is why kicking inside when you when you
when you bring that combination of power
length and then the foot speed and short
area quickness that that's a really
really really tough down for a guard and
um which is why we think he can win in
there more consistently if he can if we
can get him going on reps.
>> Hi Kendrick Eastston for USA Sports. You
mentioned yesterday that you felt like
you had just kind of scratched the
surface about what you're capable of
doing in the NFL. Can you elaborate on
some of the things you think you can do
better in this league?
>> Yeah, like uh one of the things uh was
was the passer better. Um man, I I had I
had too many pressures and not enough
sacks. Uh too many times where I got to
the quarterback and uh didn't finish
that play. So, it's um like I said, it's
just so much room that I have in in in
that. It's a it's a small thing, but
it's a it's a huge thing in my mind.
Like, uh that's the that's the next
that's the next 10 to 20% that I need to
get. And uh from there, just defining
everything that I already have, making
sure that I perfect them. It going to
take some time, but I'm perfecting
myself. Yeah, for sure.
>> This is both Ricard and Kellendrick
again. I guess at what point did the NFL
become a dream for both of you guys and
how did you how did you make it here
today?
>> Um it became a dream my eighth grade
year. Uh that's when I made the
transition to receiver fully on and then
from there I uh did I fell in love with
the game and I knew I can have fun go on
and do great things with it. So that's
when I fell in love with it and had
dreams of playing in the NFL.
>> Uh I kind of fell in love with it going
into my eighth grade year. um got my
first offer going into the eighth grade
and then uh shoot from there it was just
like uh what else can I do with it and
then I figured like you know why not
take it all the way so I'm taking it all
the way.
>> Who who made that offers?
>> Uh it was UAB.
>> Chris Harris at WSMV. Mike, this is for
you. Um, you said last night you didn't
want to project any expectations, but
when you take two guys in the first
round, I'm assuming you're expecting
them to be foundational pieces of the
future of the franchise. What about
these two guys makes you believe that
they can develop into that?
>> Well, you know, a lot of the stuff I
talked about just obviously they're very
talented. That's why they're being taken
in in the first round. But um another
part of that is all these guys have to
develop no matter where they're taken
and and and what how can they get to
their ceiling and as a player and they
like I said they embody everything that
that takes them to the next level um in
their game. It's their work ethic uh
that commitment to to to being the best
you know to film watching. you know,
it's a lot of stuff that, you know, we
uncovered with our scouts really going
into school and and talking with people
and and um and what they're all about.
Um so that's why we're very confident
that um that they're going to be able to
contribute.
>> For Mike, for Mike and Robert, if you
could please both answer. Uh,
traditionally I and I know both these
guys are top top-notch, but
traditionally guys coming out of big
programs, big conferences, drafted in
the first round come out with mounds of
numbers and and both of their production
isn't maybe what you would see from a a
number four pick or a big time pass
rusher. Kell Keldrick's talked about
that. Could you talk about the degree of
projection that you're doing and and
what you thought as as you scouted them
about their production in college?
>> Yeah, I I Paul I think you're always
looking for um you know obviously the
upside and every every situation is
different um no matter what position
they're playing or or what the scheme is
and the talent and and you know um we
certainly think they're they're going to
be very productive at this level. Um,
you know, Kendrick has just talked about
it. You know, things that that he can
improve and in his game and Carnell's
played with some, you know, he's gotten
better every year and he's played with
some pretty good receivers at at Ohio
State as well. So, um, but that that's
part of, you know, when when you're
going through the whole process and
scouting is is um is is projecting, too.
And, you know, we feel like these two
guys are going to be, you know, high
level uh production pieces in in the NFL
for us.
>> Yeah. the same thing. I mean, a
production, um, it's part of the
evaluation, but it's not the entire
evaluation. Uh, you're always looking at
circumstance. You're always looking at
situations, and, uh, these two young men
are going to produce in this league. Um,
sure, you can make an argument for
Carnell that every every opportunity
that he got, he took advantage of it,
and it's not his fault that they're
blowing teams out in the first half and
and they're only playing a half a half a
game, you know? So, you can make all
kinds of uh pinpoint all those things,
but the fact of the matter is these are
two extremely talented young men and um
they're going to be very very productive
in this league.
>> Robert, from from your vantage point,
what was the process of leading up to
the number four pick and kind of merging
with the front office? Like obviously
there was a bunch of speculation about
maybe going defense, maybe fitting your
strengths at four. Just kind of how did
you guys land on Carnell from the
coaching staff perspective and and what
was your input in general? Um, well, not
not to say it's the most important
piece, but he's pretty damn important
piece, and that's that's the quarterback
and uh doing everything we can to help
him and and uh surround him with with
players who can get the ball in their
hand and go score. And so, um, Carnell
is obviously who is by far the top uh
receiver on our board and um so when we
got to four, it was very, very easy
decision to make. Mike, we talked last
week with you about uh how many older
players are coming out and and you
talked about how you have to try to
gauge how close they are to their
ceiling. Both of these guys being really
young. How much a part of the evaluation
was that?
>> Yeah, I think that can be certainly a
part of it. Um you know, these guys were
20 years old last year playing. Um and
so that's certainly a part of it. You
know, we think there's there's there's
obviously room to grow with every player
that enters the league. They have to
develop more. Um, but certainly with
these guys, I mean, um, you know, they
they have, uh, you know, a lot of
potential here to to get even better
than they are right now. For sure.
>> Carell,
this team last year lacked for explosive
plays, especially in the pass game.
Obviously being picked at number four
overall, they're going to expect you to
provide some of that. What are some of
the ways you feel like you can bring
explosiveness to this offense? the same
way I bring explosiveness and uh at the
collegiic level, just going out there
making the most of my opportunities and
showing the team that they can trust me
and put the ball in my hands more and
more.
>> Last few
>> uh Ben Arthur, NFL on Fox, uh Carnell,
this is for you. Um who are the
receivers that you've tried to take bits
and pieces from their game and maybe
incorporate into yours? And then the
second part is how do you describe your
approach or mentality as a receiver on
the outside?
>> Yeah. Uh all I do is watch football. So
I've watched Devonte Adams a lot. Uh
Stefon Diggs and even C Red who's here.
And then the mentality of football is
just go out there and make the most of
it. And then also just what happens when
the ball come your way. That's either
you make the play or you don't.
>> Your your GM talked last night about
your ability to contort your your body
to make unique catches. Where's that
come from?
I just think it's just coming from the
mindset just going out there. Like I
said, what happens when the ball come
your way? You just going out there and
go get the ball. And when the ball's in
the air, the team depending on you to go
out there and go make that play. So, by
any means, you got to go out there and
make that play for the team.
>> Why did that why did that produce such
laughter from your people?
>> It was just a different way to put it
the question. That's it.
>> T's
for you, Carnell. I Ohio State
obviously, you know, is known as one of
the wide receiver factories. How much
did you guys really benefit from being
able to push each other? And also with
press coverage, how personally do you
take that and what is it that makes you
feel as an ex receiver, you'll be able
to be on the ball and and beat DBs the
way you have to?
>> Uh, we take that very personal at Ohio
State. Um, like I said, I'm thankful for
the ones that came before me that
allowed me to be on the path I am today.
The older guys paved the way for the
younger guys, so I'm thankful for them.
And then also we just learn from each
other. Um whether that's different moves
to run on the field or just even off the
field how each guy had their own
routine. So just learning from each
other and perfecting our own routine.
>> And also about that press coverage.
>> Oh yeah, press in the NFL in the league.
You just got to know how to win or
one-on-one coverages. So that's all it's
about. You got to take that very
personal. The team's going to rely on
you to go out there and win that
oneonone match up with the top corner on
the other side of you. So that's very
personal. And the and the biggest thing
in the in the league is can you win uh
one to one coverage. So yeah,
>> this is this is for both of you again.
You guys known each other before last
night and what was the plane ride like?
What's it kind of like knowing that
you're kind of in this together moving
forward?
>> Uh shoot. I seen him one time before. Uh
we shot basketball together, but that's
about it. Um plane ride. Playing ride
was cool. like um man it's uh it's
exciting like to to have this this kind
of caliber player uh you know get
drafted in the first round with me is uh
is a blessing in itself and I'm I can't
wait to get to get to know him and uh
you know get to be a teammate for him.
>> Yeah, that's how we met. We met on a uh
on a little trip. He carried me a
basketball. He was out there shooting
those out there disappointing them. So
yeah, and then for them we just chopped
it up. Yeah.
>> You played basketball in high school,
didn't you? I did.
>> How'd that turn out? Y'all have any 101
action?
>> Oh, no, no, no, no. We ain't doing no.
>> Last one.
>> Uh, this question is for Robert. Um,
yesterday Kellendrick had a pretty
candid moment where he said he didn't
know much about the Titans or the NFL in
general. How much of maybe that
transparency and accountability at such
a young age fits the culture that you
guys are trying to build here?
>> No, for sure. That's a good one. Um, you
know, transparency is everything.
Communication is everything. um being
able to speak your mind and have
confidence that you can walk right into
your coach's office and tell them what's
on your mind and uh try to try to nip
whatever negativity is flowing through
your head. Just try to try to get it out
and try to get it solved. So, um you
know what, he's they're both extremely
young, which is awesome. Um they're both
haven't even scratched the surface of
what we think they're capable of. And um
and and Mike hit it on the head um in
his opening statement. These two are
elite character men who have elite work
ethic and um they're they're going to
find a way to get better. They're going
to maximize who they are.
>> All right. Thanks, guys. Jersey sub. Get
some pictures.